http://www.marcjacobs.com/legal-copy/privacy-policy.html#9

Remember Me
forgot password?
Google
Forgot Password?
WE WILL SEND A PASSWORD RESET LINK TO YOUR EMAIL
SUBMIT
Privacy Policy | Marc Jacobs
Date revised and posted: May 26, 2020
Marc Jacobs International, LLC and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “MJI” “We” “Us” or “Our”) respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information (or “personal information”) We collect on this website (“MJI Website”) and any other website, mobile device application, social media Internet property or related services owned or operated by MJI (collectively, the “Sites”). MJI will be the owner and data controller of any personal information collected from you via the Site(s). This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information collected through any other website, including other sites owned or controlled by LVMH Moët Hennessy Louis Vuitton (“LVMH”) or its subsidiaries or affiliates. From time to time, MJI may modify this Privacy Policy. In that event, the modified Privacy Policy will appear at this location. In certain circumstances, you may be notified of such changes by email or other means. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and is part of, the MJI “Terms of Use” which govern your use of the Sites. Your access to and use of the Sites is undertaken at your own risk. If you do not want your personal information used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, then We recommend that you do not visit the Sites or otherwise disclose any personal information to Us.
NOTE FOR INTERNATIONAL USERS: If you are accessing the Sites from outside of the United States of America (“United States”) and place an order, then you will be subject to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of MJI's international fulfillment partner, Global-e US Inc. (“Global-e”), 79 Madison Avenue, New York, New York 10016, which may be found here.Global-e will be a data controller in its own right in respect of any personal information it holds to arrange delivery or tracking for example, such as your name, address and other contact information. Please review Global-e's terms and policies before placing an order with Global-e through the Sites. Global-e may share personal information with Us and, in that event, We will treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You further understand that your personal information is being sent to the United States, whose laws may not provide the same protections as those in your country (see the “Data Transfer” section below for more information).
For further information on how We process your personal information, please use the links below to jump to the listed section:
1. Purpose
2. What Personal Information Is Collected
3. How do We Collect Personal Information?
4. How is the Collected Personal Information Used?
Use of Cookies and Other Automated Technologies
Interest-Based Advertising
5. When Do We Share Personal Information and Usage Information with Others?
The LVMH Family
Co-Sponsored Contests, Sweepstakes and Offerings
Service Providers
Legally Compelled Disclosures
Business Transfer
6. How Long We Retain Personal Information
7. Your Choices
8. Your Rights
1. Purpose
Your privacy is important to Us. This Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of Our commitment to combine the finest quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with Our customers. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information We collect about you when you visit Our Sites, how We collect it, how We use it, with whom We share it, how long we retain it, and your choices and rights regarding Our use of this personal information. We also describe the measures We have adopted to protect your personal information and how you can contact Us about Our privacy practices.
As a general matter, We collect personal information to deliver the products and services you request, to help improve your shopping experience, and to support our business functions. These purposes include auditing interactions with consumers, detecting security incidents, performing services on behalf of the business, debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing functionality, internal research for technological development and demonstration, and activities to verify or maintain the quality and safety of MJI's website and other business undertakings.
2. What Personal Information Is Collected?
MJI may collect the following categories of personal information (as enumerated in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA)):
Identifiers – including real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifiers, online identifiers, email address, and account name.
Information in customer records – including name, signature, address, telephone number, driver's license or state identification card number, credit card number, and debit card number.
Protected classification information – including gender, race, and ethnicity.
Commercial purchasing information – including records of products and services purchased.
Internet activity – including browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer's interaction with the MJI website.
Employment or Education information – including job and education background.
Inferences – including profiles drawn from the above informational categories to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, attitudes, or other personal characteristics.
We may also keep a record of your product interests and purchases online and in stores. You may be able to send information about Our products and services to your friends and family members through the Sites by clicking on an “Email to Friend” or similar button on the Sites or in an email that We have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward Our email on your own), you may provide the name and email address of your friend or family member to Us. You may also be able to send an online card or message to a friend or family member, or send them a gift or gift certificate. If so, you may be required to provide Us with your friend's or family member's personal information. Please ensure the recipient's contact information or other personal information is accurate and that he or she has consented to such sharing or receiving email communications from Us. The personal information you provide about the recipient will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We collect the personal information described in this section only if you choose to share such information with Us. If you choose not to provide the personal information We request, then We may not be able to respond to your or provide you with Our products services, as permitted by law.
3. How do We Collect Personal Information
We collect personal information from you in two ways: (1) information We directly receive from you and (2) information We receive from others through cookies and other technologies.
User-Provided Information
Personal information We receive from you includes that which you actively share with us, such as your activity on Our website, including when you complete online forms, register or subscribe for accounts or electronic newsletters or features on the Sites, make online purchases, enter sweepstakes or contests, complete surveys, post materials, contribute to a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum that We may make available on or through the Sites, submit a comment or question to Us using the “Contact” feature or similar feature on the Sites, or send Us an email or in any other way submit personal information to Us via Our Sites.
Information We Obtain Through Cookies and Other Technologies
Personal information We receive from others through cookies and other technologies helps Us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality of Our services to you, and prevent and detect fraud. We receive personal information, such as users who came to Our Sites but did not purchase goods, from various third-party sources.
When you interact with Our Sites, We obtain certain personal information using cookies, web beacons (including pixels and tags), web server logs and other automated technologies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server.
We may use these automated technologies to collect personal information about your equipment, browsing actions, and usage patterns. The personal information We obtain in this manner may include your device IP Address and other identifiers associated with your device, domain name, location, language preferences, web browser characteristics, and device characteristics. We may also record the referring website or search engine that brought you to the Sites; the pages you visit on the Sites; the website you visit after the Sites; the ads you view or click on; your product interests and purchases; any search terms you have entered on the Sites or a referral site; and other web usage activity. With respect to location information, We collect information (1) when a user subscribes to Our Newsletter, in which case We capture the user's full shipping, billing, and IP addresses and the information provided by the user's browser, including language and country setting and (2) when a purchase is made, in which case We capture the user's full shipping, billing, and IP addresses and the information provided by the user's browser, including language and country setting.
To learn more about cookies and the other automated technologies We use, and to learn how to change your cookie settings, click here. To the extent required by applicable law, We will obtain your consent for using cookies or similar technologies.
4. How Is the Collected Personal Information Used?
We use the collected personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and rely on a number of legal bases to do so, including where (1) necessary for the performance of a contract with you or to take pre-contractual steps at your request; (2) necessary for Our legitimate business interests or those of third parties; (3) necessary for compliance with a legal obligation, a court order, or to exercise or defend legal claims; or (4) you consent to the processing, which consent you can withdraw at any time.
We use the personal information We collect where necessary to perform a contract with you or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract, including to (1) provide customer support; (2) transact with you and provide you with Our products and services; (3) process and fulfill your order and keep you informed about the status of your order; and (4) create and manage your account with MJI.
In addition, We use the personal information We collect if We have a legitimate interest to do so, including to (1) operate, develop, evaluate and improve the Sites and Our business (including developing new products and services; enhancing and improving Our products and services; managing Our communications; analyzing Our products and services and customer base; analyzing the effectiveness of Our marketing efforts; performing data analytics; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions); (2) personalize and improve your experience with Our Sites and Our products and services; (3) send you promotional materials and other communications (for example, emails, mailings, newsletters and the like); (4) communicate with you about Our products and services; (5) communicate with you and administer your participation in contests, sweepstakes, events, surveys or market research; (6) protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other liabilities; (7) reduce credit risk and manage collections; (8) improve security and administer the Sites; and (9) comply with relevant industry standards and policies, including this Privacy Policy and Our Terms of Use.
We also process your personal information to comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements to which We are subject and for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
FOR USERS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES: To the extent required by applicable law, if We plan to use the personal information We obtain for any other purpose, then We will provide an additional notice to you to describe the purposes for which We will use the personal information and Our legal basis for doing so.
FOR USERS WHO ARE CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: We do not sell personal information for monetary consideration.
Use of Cookies and Other Automated Technologies
We use personal information collected through cookies, web beacons, web server logs and other automated means to (1) remember your personal information so you will not have to re-enter it; (2) track and understand how you use and interact with the Sites; (3) tailor Our products and services around your preferences; (4) measure the usability of Our Sites and the effectiveness of Our communications; and (5) otherwise manage and enhance the Sites and Our products and services, and help ensure they are working properly. Please see Our Cookie Policy here for more information and for instructions on how to change your cookie preferences.
We also use third-party analytics services on Our Sites, which use cookies and similar automated technologies to collect data (such as IP address) to evaluate use of and interaction with Our Sites. To the extent required by applicable law, We will obtain your consent before using cookies for analytics purposes.
On Our Sites, We use the tracking technology (1) Demandware Analytics - We use Demandware Analytics to help administer and optimize the ecommerce portions of Our Sites; (2) Channel Intelligence by Google - We use this tool to track orders, sales and traffic on Our Sites. We use this information to improve Our Sites and the e-commerce experience; (3) DoubleClick, DoubleClick Floodlight, Google Tag Manager and Marin Search Marketer - We use these tracking tools to track user behavior over time and across third-party sites to improve the effectiveness of Our online advertising; (4) We collect information about what ads users view and whether they click on the ads. We use this information to improve and customize Our advertising; and (5) Google Analytics - We use Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use Our Sites. For example, We collect details of Our Sites where the visitor has come from and the total number of times a visitor has been to Our Sites.
To learn more about these analytics services and how to opt out, please visit the relevant websites for these companies, such as Google Analytics which is listed here and here.
Interest-Based Advertising
When you visit the Sites, both We and certain third-parties (such as Our advertising networks, digital advertising partners and social media platforms) collect information about your online activities, over time and across third-party websites (such as on websites that serve our ads). We may use such information to provide you with tailored advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We also may obtain information for this purpose from third-party websites on which Our ads are served. You may see certain ads on other websites because We engage third-party ad buying networks (such as Facebook and Google). Through such buying networks, We can target Our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based and contextual means. The information Our ad networks may collect on Our behalf includes data about your visits to websites that serve MJI ads, such as the pages or ads you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on Our Sites and on third-party websites that participate in these ad networks. This process helps us track the effectiveness of Our marketing efforts.
To learn how to opt out of this ad network interest-based advertising, click aboutads.info/choices and networkadvertising.org/choices. In the European Union, please visit here. To the extent required by applicable law, We will obtain your consent before using your personal information for interest-based advertising.
To learn more about how these companies serve ads to you and how to exercise your choices (such as changing your cookie preferences), click here.
5. When Do We Share Personal Information and Usage Information with Others?
We do not disclose personal information We collect about you, except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The LVMH Family
MJI is part of the LVMH corporate family. MJI, together with LVMH and its affiliates, are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “LVMH Family.” Unless you opt out as described in the “Your Choices” section below, We may share your personal information among the LVMH Family for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We will only do this to the extent permitted by applicable law. A list of the current members of the LVMH Family may be found here.
Co-Sponsored Contests, Sweepstakes and Offerings
Some of Our contests, sweepstakes and other offerings that are made available on or through the Sites from time to time may be co-sponsored by another company. In those situations, unless you instruct Us otherwise, the personal information We obtain from you in connection with such contest, sweepstakes or offering may be shared with Our co-sponsor and in accordance with terms disclosed in such contest, sweepstakes or offerings. In those situations, Our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies and in particular in accordance with any specific disclosures made to you at the time you participate in such contest, sweepstakes or offering. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of Our co-sponsors.
Service Providers
We use third party partners to provide Our e-commerce solution and to help operate the Sites and deliver Our products and services. We may share your personal information with third party e-commerce solution partners, Our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through the Sites or for Our business (such as loyalty program or membership program service providers, site hosting or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, wireless device applications, or other similar service providers that use such information on Our behalf). With respect to payment processing, for United States sales, We interface directly with Our partner Radial, which then shares your information with payment providers (e.g., PayPal) for the purpose of processing payments. Similarly, for international sales, We interface directly with Our partner Global-e, which then shares your information with one of its payment processors for the purpose of payment processing. Neither Radial nor Global-e uses your information for any purpose other than payment processing. As required by law, all service providers have entered into legally binding agreements requiring them to (1) use personal information only as necessary to perform services on Our behalf and (2) implement appropriate data security and confidentiality obligations, in accordance with applicable law.
Legally Compelled Disclosures
We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property rights and other rights. We may disclose personal information and other information when We believe it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities to protect MJI or Our customers or when We believe that disclosure is required by the law or legal process. We may disclose user information to government authorities or to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at Our discretion or as required by law in Our good faith belief, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas and as otherwise required in connection with a judicial or government proceeding or legal process. This may include in connection with the enforcement of this Privacy Policy or Our Terms of Use. We also may disclose user information when We have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interfering with Our rights or property, other users of the Sites, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.
Business Transfer
We also reserve the right to transfer personal information We have about you in the event We, Our affiliates, or any entity of the LVHM Family, sell or transfer all or a portion of Our business or assets (including in the event of a merger, acquisition, joint venture, reorganization, divestiture, dissolution or liquidation).
6. How Long We Retain Personal Information
To the extent permitted by applicable law, We typically retain personal information We obtain about you for as long as it is needed (1) for the purposes for which We obtained it, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which generally means that We will keep your personal information for the duration of Our relationship or as long as you keep your account open with us; or (2) to take into account applicable statute of limitation periods and comply with mandatory applicable laws. As described in the “Your Rights” section of this Privacy Policy, to the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may request that We delete your information or restrict the processing of such information by contacting us as indicated below.
7. Your Choices
We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information We collect about you. For example, at the time you are requested to provide personal information on the Sites, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from Us. If you wish to opt out of Our correspondence, you may also do so at any time by updating your communication preferences at marcjacobs.com and clicking the “Unsubscribe” feature or by contacting Us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section. You may also opt out of MJI's promotional emails at any time by clicking on the opt-out link within the email you receive. Please note that it may take up to up to ten business days for your request to become effective and during such time you may receive email notifications from MJI. If you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from Us, We may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with Us. Also, unless required by applicable law, We will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your personal information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.
Where required by applicable law, We will obtain your consent to send you marketing communication and newsletters about Our products and services, and invite you to participate in events, contests, sweepstakes and surveys.
To learn more about managing your preferences in relation to the data We collect on an automated basis, please see here. Certain web browsers allow you to instruct your browser to send Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals to websites you visit, informing those sites that you do not want your online activities to be tracked. Our Sites check whether user DNT settings are turned. When they are turned on, We act accordingly to prohibit tracking, which may impact the product recommendations and other features that users see on Our Sites.
8. Your Rights
To the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may request access to the personal information We maintain about you or request that We correct, update, amend, or delete your information, or restrict the processing of such information by contacting Us as indicated below. As permitted by the laws in your jurisdiction, you also may review and correct the personal information that has been collected by MJI and is stored in your user account on the MJ Website by logging in at “MyMJ” or by resubmitting your information using the “Subscribe” feature located on the MJI Website or by contacting Us as indicated below.
Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to receive, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, the personal information that you have provided to Us about you, with your consent or based on a contract to which you are party. Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to have this information transmitted to another company, where it is technically feasible.
To exercise these rights, please contact Us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section below. If you are a resident of the EEA, you also may lodge a complaint with a data protection authority if you are not satisfied with Our response, in particular in the EEA country of your habitual residence, place of work, or of an alleged infringement of the EU General Data Protection Regulation.
We will endeavor to respond to your request as soon as practicable and in compliance with applicable law. Before We are able to respond to your request, however, We may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help Us address your request.
9. Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, you have the right to: (1) request a copy of the specific personal information We have collected about you within the previous twelve months, including personal information We have shared with another company for a business purpose, (2) request that We delete your personal information, and/or (3) request that We stop selling your personal information.
Such requests may be made up to two times in a rolling twelve-month period. When You make such a request, the personal information provided may be limited to personal information We collect about you in the previous twelve months. With respect to deletion requests, note that, if you choose to delete your personal information, then you may not be able to use certain website or in-store functions that require personal information to operate. With respect to selling requests, note that We do not sell your personal information for monetary consideration. However, under some circumstances a transfer of personal information to a third party without monetary consideration may be considered a “sale” under California law. For purposes of California law, all categories of personal information, except for background and criminal information, biometric information, and government identifiers, may be transferred internally or to third parties. Such transfers may be considered a sale. We will not discriminate against you choosing to exercise your right opt out of having your personal information sold as defined under California law.
If you are a California resident, you also have the right to ask Us one time each year if We have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We share personal information with third parties for the direct marketing of their products only if We have your affirmative consent (opt in).
California residents may make such requests in three ways: (1) by sending Us an email at legal@marcjacobs.com, (2) by calling Us at 1-877-707-6272, or (3) by writing to Us at Marc Jacobs International, LLC, Attn: General Counsel – Legal Department, 72 Spring Street, 11th Floor, New York, New York 10012.
10. Data Transfers
The personal information that We collect from you or that We may receive from third parties, including Global-e, will be processed by MJI in the United States. We also may share this information with Our affiliates, including those located in the United States. In addition, Our service providers may be located in countries other than the country in which you originally provided your personal information, including in France where, along with the United States, Global-e hosts some user personal information. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you provided the personal information. In particular, the United States has not been recognized by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of data protection. When We transfer your personal information to other countries, We will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.
If you are located in the European Union (“EU”) or Switzerland, We will comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal information to recipients in countries outside of the EU that have not been recognized as providing an adequate level of data protection. In this event, We will implement appropriate safeguards, including by entering into data transfer agreements based on the European Commission's standard contractual clauses in accordance with Article 46 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation, or selecting U.S. service providers that are certified to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield. You may obtain a copy of these safeguards by contacting Us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section below. Similarly, we will comply with the applicable data transfer laws of other countries.
11. Security
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.
12. Third-Party Features
Our Sites may provide links to other online services for your convenience and information, and may include third-party features such as apps, tools, widgets and plug-ins (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). These online services and third-party features may operate independently from Us. The privacy practices of the relevant third parties, including details on the information they may collect about you, is subject to the privacy statements of these parties, which We strongly suggest you review. To the extent any linked online services or third-party features are not owned or controlled by Us, MJI is not responsible for these third parties' information practices.
Please be aware that if you disclose personal information on social media sites, website message boards or chat areas, that information may be collected and used by third parties without Our knowledge and may result in unsolicited communications from third parties. Such activities are beyond Our control and subject to those third parties' privacy statements.
13. Children’s Privacy
MJI is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. Our Sites are designed for a general audience and are not directed at children. Accordingly, We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 (or other age where parental consent may be required) without prior verifiable parental or guardian consent when legally required. If We become aware that We have inadvertently received personal information from a customer without the legally required prior verifiable parental or guardian consent, We will delete such information from Our records.
14. How to Contact Us
Marc Jacobs International LLC, 72 Spring Street, New York, New York 10012, +1-212-965-4000 (or 1-877-707-6272 if dialing within the United States) is the data controller and is responsible for the processing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy has been developed out of respect for the privacy preferences and choices of Our customers. Questions or comments may be directed to: Tel: +1-212-965-4000 (or 1-877-707-6272 if dialing within the United States), email: legal@marcjacobs.com.
Close
This site uses cookies to help us provide you with the best Marc Jacobs shopping experience. If you continue to browse our site, you consent to receive cookies as further described here.
You must be over 18, a resident of the U.S. and meet additional eligibility criteria to qualify. Late fees may apply. Estimated payment amounts shown on product pages exclude taxes and shipping charges, which are added at checkout. Loans to California residents made or arranged pursuant to a California Finance Lenders Law license. © 2020 Afterpay
Know more about complete terms.
